https://www.mitchell-electronics.com/privacy-policy/

MenuHomeProductsSoftware PortalSupportTrainingSubmit Support FormRMA RequestVideosDocumentsBlogContactRequest a QuoteAbout UsHistoryMission and VisionCareersTermsWarranty (non-MEI products)Privacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyPRIVACY POLICYPlease Read Carefully Before Using the www.mitchell-electronics.com WebsiteIntroductionThis is the Privacy Policy of Mitchell Electronics, Inc. (“we”, “us”, or “our”) for www.mitchell-electronics.com (the “Site”). Please do not use the Site if the terms of this Policy are not acceptable to you.This Policy May ChangeWe may change this Policy from time to time without notice to you. We will not notify you personally of changes made to this Policy. Please review this Policy each time that you visit the Site to make sure that its terms are acceptable to you. Collection and Use of Information We will collect information regarding your use of the Site. Some of that information will personally identify you. When you visit the Site, severs and other equipment may automatically collect information about your activity on the Site and how you connected to the Site. If you conduct a transaction through the Site, you will tell us who you are, how to contact you, and where to send things to you. You may also send us messages through the Site. We may use information that personally identifies you to (a) process and complete transactions between you and us, (b) respond to your inquiries, provide you notices, and otherwise communicate with you, (c) send you advertisements or promotional materials, (d) personalize your access to and use of the Site, (e) perform analytical analysis of your use of the Site, and (f) diagnose and resolve problems that you have with the Site. Some of these activities will require that we disclose information that personally identifies you to third parties. We may also use information that personally identifies you to establish or preserve legal claims or defenses, comply with legal obligations, or respond to law enforcement investigations. Other information that we collect regarding your use of the Site will not personally identify you, for example, pages that you view in the Site, search terms that you use in the Site, the dates and times that you visit the Site, the length of your visits to the Site, the name of the domain from which you access the Site, your Internet Protocol (IP) address, and the type of web browser software you use. We may use information that does not personally identify you to analyze the performance of the Site, make changes to the Site, develop new or other products or services, transact Site related business with others, and otherwise as permitted by law. If information that we collect regarding your use of the Site is protected by a law that is applicable to us, we will handle that information in accordance with that law. The Site is not directed to children under the age of 13 and does not request or collect information that allows the determination of a user’s age. If our assets are acquired in a business sale or similar transaction, the information that we have collected regarding your use of the Site may be transferred to the acquirer and may be used by the acquirer in the same way that we are permitted to use it. WE HAVE NO RESPONSIBILITY OR LIABILITY FOR OR RELATING TO THE PRIVACY POLICIES OF ANY OTHER WEBSITE, OR THE MANNER IN WHICH ANY DATA IS COLLECTED OR HANDLED BY ANY OTHER WEBSITE. Cookies A “cookie” is a small file that is stored on your hard drive and contains information about your computer. We may set a cookie on your computer. We use cookies to track Site patterns and practices, identify return visitors to the Site, and personalize Site experience. You can configure your browser so that it rejects cookies, but that may limit your ability to use some of the Site’s features. When you link to another website from the Site, that website may set a cookie on your computer. Advertisements, Links, and Social Media Plug- InsWe may place third party advertisements (by persons or entities other than us), links to other websites, or social media plug-ins in the Site. You will not consider those advertisements, links, or plug-ins as endorsements of any kind by us. Your use of any website that is linked to the Site will be subject to the usage agreements and privacy and other policies of that website. You will not link the Site to any other website without our express written consent.California ResidentsWe do not disclose personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes.Questions or SuggestionsIf you have any questions or suggestions for us with regard to this Policy, you can send them to us at sales@mitchell-electronics.com.Effective DateThe effective date of this Policy is December 11, 2017. This Policy supersedes and replaces all prior Privacy Policies for the Site.SEARCH
ADDRESS AND PHONEMitchell Electronics, Inc. 1005 E State St, Ste A Athens, OH 45701 United StatesP: 888-768-2771 P: 740-594-8532 F: 740-594-8533Business Hours: 9am - 5pm Eastern TimeNAVIGATIONHomeContactRequest a QuoteMITCHELL ELECTRONICS, INC.Motion Control Product since 1979.
Encoder Testing Equipment Servomotor Repair Equipment Servomotor Training.ADDRESS AND PHONEMitchell Electronics, Inc. 1005 E State St, Ste A Athens, OH 45701 United StatesP: 888-768-2771 P: 740-594-8532 F: 740-594-8533Business HoursAll times are Eastern TimeMonday - Friday9:00 am - 5:00 pmREQUEST A QUOTE
© Copyright Mitchell Electronics, Inc.HomeContactRequest a Quote
